

ARTHUR M. SANTOS Front-End Developer

Contact

Phone +34 644 350 581

E-mail arthurfms@yahoo.com

Linkedin arthur-fms

Skills

Portuguese (Brazilian)

Spanish

English

JavaScript

CSS

HTML

Excel

SOL

Python

Software Development and Journalism graduated, working as Data Implementation Specialist at Doctoralia Spain.

I have over a year experience working with big databases maintenance and manipulation, developing and managing process and technical support. I also have experience working with multicultural teams, talking in portuguese, english and spanish about technical issues.

Work History

Data Implementation Specialist - Doctoralia España

2021-05 -Current

Management and manipulation of big databases to generate specific formats, necessaries to new clients implementations. Process organization and maintenance to guarantee data protection and information quality in company system.

Contacting with all involved teams, keeping the process flowing to ensure that every step works as the company standards, and training new import members.

Data Analyst - Doctoralia Brasil

Improve data analysis for Marketing, lead generation and DP phone 2021-03 operations, update and maintenance workflows to optimize data collection. 2021-05 Generate dashboards and data insights for all related teams, focusing on new leads, keep and improve operation control, goals update and team commission standard.

Support Analyst - Doctoralia Brasil

Provide support for employees and users with doubts, bugs corrections with 2019-09 scripts on SaaS, Marketplace and financial system. Report weakness, find 2021-03 solutions to prevent bugs, and notify developers about necessary corrections by Jiras. Data report creation and analysis based on Support and Customer Success actions and needs.

> Helped client migration service improvement on support side actions, changing the avarege time from +20 working hours to a 4 working hours.

Customer Success Analyst - Doctoralia Brasil

2019-04 -2019-09

Assist health professionals from Chile by phone and email. Made usability training and helping them with platform issues, setting the environment for new clients and keeping track of their needs. Follow client's engagement and guarantee the best usage from the system, generating best results and helping them to achieve their goals.

Trilingual Call Center Agent - Sykes Brasil

2018-09 -2019-04

Manage corporate cards request in English, Portuguese and Spanish. Credit card limit raises requests, account information and client needs. Receive and follow client's request, managing their information following all companies process.

Academic background

2020-01 -**Technology in Systems Analysis and Development**

2022-06 UniCesumar - Curitiba, PR. Brazil.

Bachelor Degree in Journalism 2013-01 -

2017-12 Universidade Metodista de São Paulo - São Paulo, SP, Brazil.

Extracurricular activities

2022-02 -Web Development Bootcamp - Practicum by Yandex 2023-01

2022-01 -Front-End Engineering at EBAC 2023-01

Java Object-Oriented Development course at Universidade Estadual 2020-05 -

2020-07 do Ceará